CONTACT



647-401-8005



aartho95@gmail.com



github.com/aa-thomas



Brampton, ON, Canada

EDUCATION

Juno College Institute of Technology

Web Development

General Education Diploma

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Adaptability
- Complex problem-solving
- Communication
- Time Management
- Paired programming & teambased development
- Project scope management
- HTML5
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Node.js
- SQL
- Git

AARON THOMAS

FULL-STACK JAVASCRIPT WEB DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a full-stack web developer with over one year of experience building both front-end and back-end projects with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js and SQL.. I am currently looking to turn my passion and hobby into employment. I am an eager learner looking to join a team with solid mentorship, where I can develop my skills .while also being able to contribute as much as possible.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

SQL Library Manager

 Web application for listing, adding, updating, and deleting books in a library.

Object-Oriented-

Programming Phrase Game

 A browser based word guessing game using OOP principles

React Gallery App

 A fast and lightweight gallery app that returns pictures based on a users search

Public API Requests

 A mock employee directory using the Random User Generator API

WORK EXPERIENCE

Forklift Operator

June 2017 - September 2022

- Member and contributor to Warehouse Guiding Team during \$900,000
 repovation.
- Use keen organizational and time management skills to process thousands of bottles per day
- Contributed to 24.75% revenue increase from 2018 -2021

Labatt Brewing Company January 2016 - June 2017

- · Operated double counter-balance forklift.
- Contributing Member to Health and Safety Team
- Manage/ troubleshoot product delivery system
- Exceeded daily target KPI of 600 layers regularly

Best Buy Inc.

December 2013 - January 2016

- Identify customer needs quickly and turn into technology based solutions
- Successfully diffused customer issues using patience and excellent listening skills
- Able to suggestively sell/upsell products and services